Travis Smith

11 Armour Close, Kingston 9 St.Andrew Cell: 594-8660 – <u>travissmith94@hotmail.com</u>

Summary

Currently an undergraduate Computer Science student at the University of the West Indies Mona set to graduate in 2016. Strong problem solving and programming skill. Fluent in programming languages: Python, Ruby, C and Java as well languages (Javascript, CSS, HTML).

Skills

- Web Development with Ruby on Rails and Play! Framework
- Android mobile application development
- Experience with Test-Driven and Behaviour Driven development approached
- Experience in use of Linux and Windows environments
- Strong Problem Solving Skills

Accomplishments

Graduated First in class in Computer Science from Campion College sixth form. Qualified for ACM Inter-Collegiate Programming competition 2015 Placed in the top 500 globally in the IEEExtreme Programming Competition 2015 Current GPA 3.9

Experience

IT Intern

May 2015 to Current

Artuvic IT Solutions – Mona, Kingston

Collaborated with members of the development team in modifying a web api and associated mobile application for Doorway Express Ltd. Using the Play! Java Framework and Android SDK.

IT Intern

June 2014 to September 2014

Artuvic IT Solutions – Mona, Kingston

Collaborated with development team in the creation of a web application using the Play! framework and Android SDK.

Marketing Intern

June 2012 to September 2012

Sangster's Bookstores – Kingston

Assisted the Marketing Department in the preparation of books for promotional events as well as the

sale and promotion of books at events

IT Intern

July 2011 to August 2011

National Works Agency – Kingston

Assisted IT department in diagnosis and repair of technical issues and the installation and upgrading of computer systems

Education

Sixth form: 2012

Campion College – St. Andrew Jamaica

Cape passes in : Computer Science , Physics , Chemistry , Biology , Pure Mathematics , Carribean

Studies and Communication Studies

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science, 2016

University of the West Indies Mona Software Architecture coursework Coursework in Computer Science, Electronics and Physics